and I lead the team that put together this specialization.
líder da equipe que montou esta especialização.
In this module, we will go back and revisit an important concept called embeddings.
Neste módulo, revisitaremos um conceito importante chamado incorporação.
In this course, we're looking at a variety of things
Neste curso, veremos diversas coisas
that every ML practitioner should have in their toolkit.
que todo profissional de ML precisa saber.
We're talking about the art and science of machine learning.
Estamos falando sobre a arte e a ciência do aprendizado de máquina.
Let's now look in detail at the advantages that embeddings provide us.
Vamos ver com detalhes as vantagens da incorporação.
In this module, you will learn how to use embeddings to manage sparse data;
Neste módulo, você verá como usar incorporações
to make machine learning models that use
e fazer com que os modelos de aprendizado de máquina que usam
sparse data consume less memory and train faster.
dados esparsos consumam menos memória e treinem mais rápido.
Embeddings are also a way to do dimensionality reduction and in that way,
As incorporações também são uma maneira de reduzir a dimensão
So we will use embeddings as a way to reduce the dimensionality of
Usaremos as incorporações como uma maneira de reduzir a dimensão
problematic inputs and increase model generalization.
de entradas problemáticas e aumentar a generalização do modelo.
The embeddings also become helpful if you want to do clustering of the observations,
As incorporações também são úteis se você incluir as observações em um cluster,
but embeddings are not just about one machine learning model.
mas não são apenas um modelo de aprendizado de máquina.
Embeddings often work best when you think about families of machine learning models.
Elas muitas vezes funcionam melhor com famílias de modelos.
The embedding created on one model can be
As incorporações de um modelo podem ser usadas
used to jump-start another model in the same family.
para iniciar outro modelo da mesma família.
So you will learn how to create reusable embeddings.
Você verá como criar incorporações reutilizáveis.
Embeddings are so useful,
As incorporações são tão úteis
that creating and embedding can be thought
que a criação delas pode ser vista
of as a machine learning problem in its own right.
como um problema de aprendizado de máquina.
You might have a team maintaining
Você pode ter uma equipe para manter
particularly important embeddings that are used widely throughout an enterprise.
incorporações importantes usadas em toda a empresa.
Think of a good reusable embedding as being similar to a software library.
Pense em uma incorporação reutilizável como uma biblioteca de software.
Because embeddings are so useful,
Por serem tão úteis,
it can be helpful to visualize them,
pode ser útil visualizar as incorporações,
and TensorBoard gives us a way to do this.
e o TensorBoard oferece uma maneira de fazer isso.